# Hannah Chamorro

# Back End Web Developer



(714)457-45600



Hannah.Chamorro @gmail.com

#### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

**Analytical Thinking Problem Solving** Tolerant & Flexible Organization **Problem Solving** Team Leadership **Strong Communication** 

## LICENSES & **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certified Administrative Assistant (CAA) / 2015 CPR Certified / 2018 HIPPA Certified / 2018 PMP Certified / 2009

### REFERENCES

### John Goldsmith

Regions Financial

(210) 123-1268 john.goldsmith@regions.com Direct Manager/Supervisor

#### Mark Adler

Regions Financial

(210) 123-1265 mark.adler@regions.com Director HR



## **Career Objective**

Back-End Web Developer leveraging a background in culinary to build a more concise user experience on the web. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Development from Northwestern University, with newly developed skills in JavaScript, CSS, React.js, and responsive web design.

## **Professional Experience**

## The Little Gym, Chicago, IL

Facility Manager, Jan 2016-Present

- Update and maintain local website.
- Build and cultivate social media presence.
- Establish, develop and retain positive customer relationships.
- Develop and organize inventory.

## The Peninsula, Chicago, IL

Lead Cook, May 2010-Jan 2016

- Experience working in wide array of high-pressure environments.
- Met business deadlines daily.
- Ability to organize and prioritize workload effectively.
- Flexible and adaptable to change.

#### The Resort at Pelican Hill, Newport Beach, CA

Lead Cook, Sept 2008- May 2010

- Lead opening team of luxury resort.
- Communicate to multiple outlets to accomplish objectives.

#### Double Tree Hotel, Angheim, CA

Lead Cook, August 2007- August 2008

Responsible for assigning tasks, sanitation, and inventory.



## Education

## Northwestern University, Chicago IL

Coding Bootcamp, March 2020

## Cooking and Hospitality Institute of Chicago

Associate's in Applied Science, September 2007

Relevant Coursework: JavaScript, CSS, React.js, node